blinds-2go.co.uk 2019-08-30

# Blinds 2go | Privacy Policy

Taking care of your personal information is as important to us as it is to you. That's why we take every measure possible to do that carefully and sensitively. This Privacy Notice outlines the way we collect and use your personal information through Blinds 2go and its affiliate sites.

###### Personal Data That We Collect

Blinds 2 Go Ltd collects essential data to be able to complete your order. When completing an order with us, we will take your name, billing address, contact telephone number, email address and where applicable, a separate delivery address. Payment details are also taken for orders where payment is required.

* * *

###### How We Use Personal Data

Blinds 2 Go Ltd uses the data that we collect to provide you with the product that you have ordered from our website. Your name is taken so we can address our communications to you and also so that your parcel is dispatched for your attention. Your billing address is taken to allow validation of your payment details and where applicable, a delivery address is taken so that the parcel can be delivered to the address that suits you best. We also take a contact telephone number so that we can contact you if there are any problems with your order and we take an email address so that we can send you order notifications and updates and any communications should we be unable to contact you by telephone. Your email address also serves as part of your log in to our order tracking service.

* * *

###### Reasons We Share Personal Data

We share your personal data as necessary to complete any transaction or provide any product you have requested or authorised. This data is shared with suppliers and couriers working on our behalf. It is also used when required by law or to respond to legal process, to protect our customers and to protect the rights or property of Blinds 2 Go Ltd. Access to your personal data is limited to information needed to perform these functions and may not be used for other purposes. Furthermore, all personal information is processed in accordance with this Privacy Notice and as permitted by applicable data protection laws.

* * *

###### Will I be contacted for marketing purposes?

By combining the data we have about you, we then use this to offer you promotions, products and services that are most likely to interest you. The data privacy law allows this as part of our legitimate interest in understanding our customers and providing the highest levels of service. 

We offer regular emails to let you know about any promotions that may be running along with any new products that we have introduced into our ranges. 

Your email address is never shared outside of Blinds 2 Go Ltd and you can unsubscribe at any stage by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any marketing email you have received from our company.

* * *

###### How Secure is Information About Me?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We do not reveal any of your credit card details when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

* * *

###### How can I see what information you have about me?

It's your right under the UK Data Protection Act to ask for a copy of your information.

We'll need to see two copies of your ID. Valid forms of ID include the following:

  * Passport
  * Driving licence
  * Birth certificate
  * Utility bill (from the last three months)
  * Current vehicle registration document
  * Bank statement (from the last three months)
  * Rent book (from the last three months)

To get in touch, email: [dpa.officer@blinds-2go.co.uk](mailto:dpa.officer@blinds-2go.co.uk)

###### Or write to:

The Data Protection Officer   
Blinds 2 Go Ltd   
1 Longwall Avenue  
Nottingham  
NG2 1NA

If you wish to make changes to the data we hold, please let us know (using the contact details above) after you have received your copy of your data and we can make alterations or erase the data if appropriate.

Of course, you can only request information regarding yourself and no other person.
